TAGAÑA, TIMOTHY JAMES LUNAR

10 Kab Martin St.

Brgy. Tinajeros, Malabon City Contact details: 09291196105 taganatimothyjames@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tjtagana/



OBJECTIVE:

To work with an organization which would provide an opportunity to grow professionally and hone my skills and utilize them to serve the organization. To take up a challenging career and grow with honesty, loyalty, good relationship, and best performance and translate my experience, knowledge, skills, and abilities into value for the company.

PERSONAL PROFILE:

Experienced Graphic Design Specialist and a novice Web Developer, highly adaptive to various multimedia skills. Creative, goal-driven, and a good team player. Music and sports enthusiast. I approach challenges as a key to success and self-development.

SKILL SUMMARY:

Programming and Web Development

- Designed and created a static mobile friendly portfolio website hosted in GitLab
- Developed an E-Commerce API using Node and Express.js
- Completed a Full-Stack Application using the MERN Stack
- Designed UI/UX for mobile and desktop using Figma

Multimedia Professional Skills

Adobe Photoshop
 Adobe Premiere Pro
 Adobe Illustrator

Autodesk Maya

Videography

Photography

3D Modeling

Cartified Full Stack Web Developer Web Page

Social Media Marketing

(2023)

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND:

Certification

Certification:	Digital/Multimedia and Information Resources Design Zuitt- Coding Bootcamp	(2023)
College:	Bachelor of Science in Entertainment and Multimedia Computing with Specialization in Digital Animation University of the East Manila	(2013 - 2017)
Secondary Education:	Carlos "Botong" National High School- Rizal	(2009-2012)
	Stella Maris Academy – La Union	(2008 - 2009)
Primary Education:	Nangalisan Elementary School- La Union	(2002-2008)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Freelance Graphic Designer – Perpetual Help Technological School Inc.

May 2019 - Present

Provides advertisement materials for promotions. Create institutional logo, letterhead, and document cover. Reports directly with business owner for development and critique of educational materials.

Graphic Design Specialist - Integreon

Jan 2020 - Jan 2022

Present creative designs for international clients. Enhance work presentation and modify slides and details based on guidelines set by the team leader. Assess final output prior submitting to quality assurance. Conducts freestyle lay out for specific projects together with the team.

Intern – Jump Digital Asia Pte. Ltd. Jun 2017 – Oct 2017

Assist the copy writer in producing creative advertisement for clients, engaging materials for leads generation, and compelling media in various platforms.

Assist the art director in drafting creative design based on the concept provided. Enhance visual aspects of various media such as photography, video, and digital arts. Assist the copy writer in producing creative advertisement for clients, engaging materials for leads generation, and compelling media in various platforms. Assist the art director in drafting creative design based on the concept provided. Enhance visual aspects of various media such as photography, video, and digital arts.

LICENSE RECEIVED:

Construction Occupational Health and Safety
Prophets Management Consultancy Services – November 2022

CHARACTER REFERENCES:

Asst. Prof. Roselle Basa Professor, University of the East Manila 0917 749 9329 Mr. Bryand Rasco Animator & Professor, University of the East Manila 0905 259 6245

I hereby declare that the statements and information in this resume are true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Timothy James L. Tagaña